Class of 1917 Records, 1913-1988
Smith College Archives
Class of 1917 Records
1913-1988
Smith College. Class of 1917.
RG 80 UUID:aed95b66-93e6-4cb3-8f6f-bbb4445611fe
21 boxes (16.46 linear ft.)
Smith College Archives Northampton, MA
This collection contains photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, and other memorabilia from the commencement and reunions of the Class of 1917.
The Class of 1917 was the thirty-ninth graduating class of Smith College.
The Class of 1917 records contain materials describing the history and activities of the Class of 1917, including materials from commencement, reunions, senior dramatics, and other important events. Types of materials include photographs, invitations, songs, newspaper clippings, letters, pamphlets, and other memorabilia.
Individual biographical files are also available, and often include photographs, photo albums, newspaper clippings, letters and correspondences, and class notes.
Information on Use
Terms of Access and Use
The records are open for research according to the regulations of the Smith College Archives without any additional restrictions.
History of the Collection
The Class of 1917 Records were created by the students and donated to the College Archives.
- Reunion Signature Book 1918-1987 (Box 1895, Folder 1)
- Oversized Group Photo undated (Box 1895, Folder 2)
- Baccalaureate Service 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 1)
- Clippings 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 2)
- Commencement 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 3)
- Commencement Music 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 4)
- Commencement Photographs 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 5)
- Freshman Frolic 1913 (Box 1896, Folder 6)
- Freshman Grind 1913 (Box 1896, Folder 7)
- Freshman Handbook 1913-1914 (Box 1896, Folder 8)
- Groups 1914-1917 (Box 1896, Folder 9)
- Ivy Day 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 10)
- Ivy Day Photographs 1917 (Box 1896, Folder 11)
- Junior Frolic 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 12)
- Junior Prom 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 13)
- Junior Ushers 1916 (Box 1896, Folder 14)
- Class Letters 1965-1988 (Box 1896, Folder 15)
- Organization 1915-1917 (Box 1896, Folder 16)
- Reunions 1922 (Box 1896, Folder 17)
- Reunions 1927 (Box 1896, Folder 18)
- Reunions 1932 (Box 1896, Folder 19)
- Reunions 1937 (Box 1896, Folder 20)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 1896, Folder 21)
- Reunions 1942 (Box 1896, Folder 22)
- Reunions 1947 (Box 1896, Folder 23)
- Reunions 1948 (Box 1896, Folder 24)
- Reunions 1952 (Box 1896, Folder 25)
- Reunions 1957 (Box 1897, Folder 1)
- Reunions 1962 (Box 1897, Folder 2)
- Reunions 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 3)
- Reunion Questionnaire: A-C 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 4)
- Reunion Questionnaire: D-G 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 5)
- Reunion Questionnaire: H-M 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 6)
- Reunion Questionnaire: N-S 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 7)
- Reunion Questionnaire: T-Y 1967 (Box 1897, Folder 8)
- Reunions 1972 (Box 1897, Folder 9)
- Reunions 1977-1982 (Box 1897, Folder 10)
- Reunions 1987 (Box 1897, Folder 11)
- Reunion Songs undated (Box 1897, Folder 12)
- Secretary's Records 1913-1915 (Box 1897, Folder 13)
- Secretary's Records 1915-1917 (Box 1897, Folder 14)
- Secretary's Records 1918-1982 (Box 1897, Folder 15)
- Senior Dramatics 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 16)
- Senior Dramatics-Photographs 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 17)
- Sophomore Reception 1915 (Box 1897, Folder 18)
- Songs undated (Box 1897, Folder 19)
- Step Sings 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 20)
- Class Supper 1917 (Box 1897, Folder 21)